

EDUCATION

BA Hons at National University

Barishal Govt. BM College 2021 - 2022

Higher Secondary Certificate-HSC

Patuakhali Govt. University College 2018 - 2020

Secondary School Certificate- SSC

Tushkhali High School, Patuakhali 2016 - 2017

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Latest Bootstrap
- Latest Tailwindcss
- Vanila JavaScript
- Jquery Animation
- React / Next Js (Learning)

WORDPRESS SKILLS

- Elementor, Divi Builder & Wp Bekary Page Builder
- ACF / CPT, JetForms Etc
- Custom User Dashboard
- Ecommerce Woocommerce Functionality
- SEO Expert [Yoast, Rank Math]
- Premium Theme Customization

LANGUAGES

BANGLA **ENGLISH**

MOHAMMAD RAHAT

Front-End Designer with Wordpress Expert

+8801715-867227

+8801601-867227

officialmrahat@gmail.com 🔀

https://mohammadrahat.com

Barishal, Patuakhali 8600, Dhaka Bangladesh

ABOUT ME

This is Mohammad Rahat. A Professional Full-stack Responsive Wordpress Website Developer & Front-end Designer. I am working remotely with client's from all over the world since 2021. I have a diverse set of experience in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap5 Tailwind Css, Vanila JavaScript, Jquery, Php & WordPress. I can build any types of website using WordPress. I've created more than 300+ WordPress & 200+ Frontend website in my web development career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Professional Front-end Specialist Reconnect | Dhaka, Bangladesh

2021 - 2022

Since The Beginning of 2022 to right now, I have been working with Reconnect IT Firm as a Front-end Specialist. For my local clien's, I have designed various websites like DarazBD, Apple Gadgets etc etc. I can copy, clone, duplicate any types of website also I have the ability to design any website base on client;s requirements from scratch.

Professional Wordpress Developer

2021-Present

Reconnect & Local Marketplace | Dhaka, Bangladesh

I've created more than 300+ Wordpress Website using various Themes & Plugins. Specially, I have core knowledge in Elementor, Divi Builder & Wp Bekary Page Builder. I have extensive knowledge with _ CPT / ACF, PSD to Wordpress, Custom User Dashboard, Wocommerce Functionality, Needed Plugin Features etc. Some of my work link: www.azmatechno.com / www.motosave.fi / www.dmxautofix.fi / www.reconnectsoft.com / www.trippers-hub.com.

Search Engine Optimization Expert - SEO

Full Website SEO

The Costume Company | Australia

I have done full website SEO for my Australian client's. I can do Keyword Research, Keyword Analysis, Content Analysis, One Page Setup, One Page SEO, Technical SEO, Google Analysis, Sitemap, KGR, Backlinks, GSC Error Fixing, etc.

CERTIFICATION / WORKSHOP

Full Stack Web Development- SSB-358

2021-22

Shikhbe Shobai Institude | Mirpur Dhaka, Bangladesh

Basic to Advance Wordpress Customization SoroBindu Institude | Dinajpur, Bangladesh

2021

REFERENCES

Mohammad Russell Graphics Designer

Phone: +8801712-104749 +8801612-104749

Email: raselsign@gmail.com

Facebook, Youtube, Google Social Media

M.RAHAT